CONOR MURPHY

CONTACT

(D) 0852512569,

conormurphy94@hotmail.com

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Typing speed of 80wpm
- Adaptability
- Problem Solving
- Logical Thinker
- People Management
- Effective Communication

PayPal awards:

 PayPal CCPH EMEA Olympics Silver Medal x2

PayPal Spot Awards #1 (Values attributed to this award are one team, customer champions.)

PROFILE

A well-organized customer support agent with invaluable experience in providing customer support. Highly focused with a comprehensive knowledge and understanding of the importance of high-quality support. A consistent track record of successfully employing best business practices that improve efficiency, reduce operating costs whilst increasing productivity. Easy going by nature and able to get along with both work colleagues and senior managers.

EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2019, 2022 - Current

Customer Support Representative *Evergreen Silk Plants*, Ardee, Louth

- Providing phone, live chat and email support for customers with any queries.
- Building a trusting relationship between the company and the clients.
- Using my research skills to assist with customer queries.

2020 - 2022

UK Business Support Agent PayPal, Dundalk, Louth

- Liaising or escalating to relevant departments to resolve customer issues.
- Exceeding company targets in areas of Average Call Time, Resolution Rate, KDI and Completed Contacts Per Hour.
- Dealing with live phone cases of fraud analyzing accounts for evidence while reassuring the customer of their protections.
- Guide both individuals and small large businesses on phone and email.
- Deal with both buyers and sellers professionally and guiding them towards amicable resolutions for disputes, while educating on standard trading practices and protections.
- Reviewing documents that have been submitted to colleagues to ensure they are credible, acceptable and compliant.

EDUCATION

Aug 2022 - Current

Code Institute: Diploma in Full Stack Software Development Modules

- HTML + CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- Django
- Full stack toolkit

European Computer Driver's License.

Modules:

- Computer Essentials
- Online Essentials
- Word Processing
- Spreadsheets
- IT Security

2014

Creative Multimedia
Drogheda Institute of Further Education